Guide to the Marthod Family Papers, 1748-1856
Department of Special Collections
Marthod Family Papers,
1748-1856
Special Collections M0307
Marthod family
.25 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Purchase from Carl Kakasuleff, 1975
Scope and Content
Letters (courtship letters, letters of condolence, familial relations) and legal civil documents (birth, marriage, statements of witness, including copies from notaries books). The primary place of origin is Gray, Haute Sa^one, France. Louis Marthod is the primary correspondent, the military and civil documents belong mainly to his immediate family.
Container List
- 1748-1705four pieces (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 1800-1801seven pieces (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 1802twelve pieces (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1803seven pieces (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1804five pieces (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1806-1808eight pieces (Box 1, Folder 6)
- 1809-1810three pieces (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 1812-1817thirteen pieces (Box 1, Folder 8)
- 1818-1823seven pieces (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1828-1856ten pieces (Box 1, Folder 10)